qubesys.com 2013-10-10

# Privacy Policy | QubeSys

Our goal is to provide an Internet experience that delivers the information, resources, and services that are most relevant and helpful to you. In order to achieve this goal, from time to time we may collect information during your visits. This Privacy Policy is designed to help you learn more about the personal information we collect, who we might share it with, and how we protect it.

**Note:** Additional terms and conditions, if any, regarding the collection and use of your information may also be provided to you before you sign up for a particular QubeSys service – privacy policies for those services will be linked from those particular areas or sections of our site.

####### What Information Do We Collect?

QubeSys collects personal information in three ways – through information provided directly from our users, from information collected through web server logs and through cookies. Our programmers have thorough knowledge of both the PayPal integration methods and can easily implement it on your website or, for your ecommerce shopping cart. If you would like references of previous work done by us in these areas, please contact us at info@qubesys.com

####### Information Supplied by Our Users

QubeSys collects personal information, such as your e-mail address, name, home or work address and telephone number. QubeSys may also collect demographic information, such as your ZIP code, age, gender, and legal interests. QubeSys does not collect any of this unique information about you except when you specifically and knowingly provide such information.
